[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9901_Yonas_Age",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Prompt_Age",
        "NPCResponse": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Response_Age"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9901_Yonas_Books",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Prompt_Books",
        "NPCResponse": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Response_Books"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9901_Yonas_BecomingSoulwarden",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Prompt_BecomingSoulwarden",
        "NPCResponse": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Response_BecomingSoulwarden"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9901_Yonas_SoulwardenFate",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Prompt_SoulwardenFate",
        "NPCResponse": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Response_SoulwardenFate"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9901_Yonas_Fort",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Prompt_Fort",
        "NPCResponse": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Response_Fort"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9901_Yonas_Friends",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Prompt_Friends",
        "NPCResponse": "@9901_MSQ_Yonas_Response_Friends"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9914_Hunter_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9914_MSQ_Hunter_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9914_MSQ_Hunter_Response_Repellent"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9915_Researcher1_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9915_MSQ_Researcher1_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9915_MSQ_Researcher1_Response_Repellent"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9916_Researcher2_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9916_MSQ_Researcher2_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9916_MSQ_Researcher2_Response_Repellent"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9917_Researcher3_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9917_MSQ_Researcher3_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9917_MSQ_Researcher3_Response_Repellent"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9918_Researcher4_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9918_MSQ_Researcher4_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9918_MSQ_Researcher4_Response_Repellent"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9907_AEVillager1_Offering",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9907_MSQ_AEVillager1_Prompt_Offering",
        "NPCResponse": "@9907_MSQ_AEVillager1_Response_Offering"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9908_AEVillager2_Offering",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9908_MSQ_AEVillager2_Prompt_Offering",
        "NPCResponse": "@9908_MSQ_AEVillager2_Response_Offering"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9906_Shamaness_Offering",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9906_MSQ_Shamaness_Prompt_Offering",
        "NPCResponse": "@9906_MSQ_Shamaness_Response_Offering"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9903_Emile_FactionSame",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Prompt_FactionSame",
        "NPCResponse": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Response_FactionSame",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9903_Emile_FactionRival",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Prompt_FactionRival",
        "NPCResponse": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Response_FactionRival",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9903_Emile_Epilogue",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Prompt_Epilogue",
        "NPCResponse": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Response_Epilogue"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9903_Emile_Origins1",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Prompt_Origins1",
        "NPCResponse": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Response_Origins1"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9903_Emile_Origins2",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Prompt_Origins2",
        "NPCResponse": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Response_Origins2"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9903_Emile_Origins3",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Prompt_Origins3",
        "NPCResponse": "@9903_MSQ_Emile_Response_Origins3"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9905_Rima_FactionSame",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Prompt_FactionSame",
        "NPCResponse": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Response_FactionSame",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9905_Rima_FactionRival",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Prompt_FactionRival",
        "NPCResponse": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Response_FactionRival",
        "RequiredFaction": "Covenant"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9905_Rima_Epilogue",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Prompt_Epilogue",
        "NPCResponse": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Response_Epilogue"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9905_Rima_Origins1",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Prompt_Origins1",
        "NPCResponse": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Response_Origins1"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9905_Rima_Origins2",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Prompt_Origins2",
        "NPCResponse": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Response_Origins2"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9905_Rima_Origins3",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Prompt_Origins3",
        "NPCResponse": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Response_Origins3"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9905_Rima_Origins4",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Prompt_Origins4",
        "NPCResponse": "@9905_MSQ_Rima_Response_Origins4"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9904_Theo_FactionSame",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Prompt_FactionSame",
        "NPCResponse": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Response_FactionSame",
        "RequiredFaction": "Syndicate"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9904_Theo_FactionRival",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Prompt_FactionRival",
        "NPCResponse": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Response_FactionRival",
        "RequiredFaction": "Marauder"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9904_Theo_Epilogue",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Prompt_Epilogue",
        "NPCResponse": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Response_Epilogue"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9904_Theo_Origins1",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Prompt_Origins1",
        "NPCResponse": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Response_Origins1"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9904_Theo_Origins2",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Prompt_Origins2",
        "NPCResponse": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Response_Origins2"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9904_Theo_Origins3",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Prompt_Origins3",
        "NPCResponse": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Response_Origins3"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9904_Theo_Origins4",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Prompt_Origins4",
        "NPCResponse": "@9904_MSQ_Theo_Response_Origins4"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9914_MSQ_Hunter_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9914_MSQ_Hunter_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9914_MSQ_Hunter_Response_Repellent",
        "AchievementUnlock": "99_MSQ_28_TopicA",
        "RequiredAchievement": "99_MSQ_28_TopicUnlock"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9915_MSQ_Researcher1_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9915_MSQ_Researcher1_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9915_MSQ_Researcher1_Response_Repellent",
        "AchievementUnlock": "99_MSQ_28_TopicB",
        "RequiredAchievement": "99_MSQ_28_TopicA"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9916_MSQ_Researcher2_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9916_MSQ_Researcher2_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9916_MSQ_Researcher2_Response_Repellent",
        "AchievementUnlock": "99_MSQ_28_TopicC",
        "RequiredAchievement": "99_MSQ_28_TopicA"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9917_MSQ_Researcher3_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9917_MSQ_Researcher3_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9917_MSQ_Researcher3_Response_Repellent",
        "AchievementUnlock": "99_MSQ_28_TopicD",
        "RequiredAchievement": "99_MSQ_28_TopicA"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9918_MSQ_Researcher4_Repellent",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9918_MSQ_Researcher4_Prompt_Repellent",
        "NPCResponse": "@9918_MSQ_Researcher4_Response_Repellent",
        "AchievementUnlock": "99_MSQ_28_TopicE",
        "RequiredAchievement": "99_MSQ_28_TopicA"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9921_Walker_Origins1",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9921_MSQ_Walker_Prompt_Origins1",
        "NPCResponse": "@9921_MSQ_Walker_Response_Origins1"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9922_Wayne_Origins1",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9922_MSQ_Wayne_Prompt_Origins1",
        "NPCResponse": "@9922_MSQ_Wayne_Response_Origins1"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9923_Constance_Origins1",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9923_MSQ_Constance_Prompt_Origins1",
        "NPCResponse": "@9923_MSQ_Constance_Response_Origins1"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9924_Eliza_Origins1",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9924_MSQ_Eliza_Prompt_Origins1",
        "NPCResponse": "@9924_MSQ_Eliza_Response_Origins1"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "9925_Samir_Origins1",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9925_MSQ_Samir_Prompt_Origins1",
        "NPCResponse": "@9925_MSQ_Samir_Response_Origins1"
    }
]